Newspaper! Read today's news!
Newspaper!
Newspaper! Newspaper!
Hi Joe.
Hi James.
Where are you going?
Daddy, I've seen your photo.
You've kept pigtail before?
When I was in the U.S. studying,
it was still in the Ching Dynasty
But after the revolution,the government
ordered everyone to cut their pigtails
But many, who are very conservative,
are unable to accept the change of government
But now we are going to Wu Dang Mountain,
and after 2 hours the train will start rolling,
but why do we still come to Shanghai?
Because we came back to China to
find the things that we want
It is rumoured to be here,
therefore I am going to have a look
Daddy, what is so important?
Wait for me here.
I'll be back soon.
Wang, take care good care of her.
Didn't we agree that this time
you won't leave me alone?
Don't worry
From now on, Daddy will not
leave you alone again
Tang Yun Long, Professor Tang?
Hmm
Please.
Professor Tang
Thank you for
coming to do the examination
Your Lordship, you are too kind
I've researched this treasure for many years
and today I can see it with my own eyes
which I consider very fortunate
Professor Tang
I've long since heard your name
You too, Mr. Paul Chen
You've combed and searched all the rare treasure
in China and you are very famous overseas
I've never thought that this mysterious
Tsuen Tien Sword is in your hand
This Tsuen Tien Sword has a
history of 2,000 years
Legend has it that the might of the
Tang Dynasty's greatness
it's all because of this sword's mysterious power
Professor Tang
Please.
Asteroid rocks is used to make this sword
It has unique quality and power
Originally it was from a mysterious tribe
After the tribe was perished in a war,
the sword disappeared
I've heard that it appeared
in Wu Dang Mountain once
Your Lordship
This sword is
USD $300,000
In future, when you've regained your country
The reward
won't be just USD $300,000
Professor Tang
Dragon Sword with Seven Powers
just like the treasure mountain
The true sutra gives freedom
to the heavenly pill
Outside the cave of the Eight
Meridian hides the black leader.
The Fiery Pearl in between the Clouds.
It seems that the myth is true
The magical sword is one of the seven treasures
What did you just said?
Seven Treasures?
Maybe...
Maybe this is a treasure map?
Tang Yun Long!
What tricks are you up to?
Tricks?
You're the one playing trick
This so called Tsuen Tien Sword is a fake!
Paul Chen! Fake white man!
How dare you cheat me!
How do I know if the two of you are not in cahoots?
I don't care whether you buy or not,
the person you've brought has broken my sword
You will have to pay!
Get the map back! Get the map back!
Wang, start the car!
Daddy, you've been fighting?
I am alright.
To the train station. Quick!
Men went to battle at the border
Woman weaving in the home land
Farming in the day
Spinning wool in the night
Don't know if it's night or day,
will still get the job done
The warriors will have food and clothing
If you don't believe
Just look at the body
Our shoes and socks
and our pants and shirts
Miss
I noticed that you have been looking at me
Do you think
I have been idolizing you?
Are you a representative of Bei Ping
to participate in
Wu Dang Martial Arts competition?
I am,
from Pin Jin,
2 towns, 2 province
and the most handsome fighter
You are beautiful
What you are wearing is also beautiful.
Do not disturb the lady!
Don't be afraid
You are going to Hubei?
For what purpose?
To rob
This lady is rather amusing!
What are you going to rob?
To rob an invitation card
For example, like this one.
You are going to rob me
of my invitation card?
You are going to Wu Dang
for competition,
then, where am I going?
Go home,
or else,
to the hospital.
How dare you play around with me!
Wudang - Invitation
Pure Land Beyond the Clouds
Purple Mist Hall
Great Wu Dang - Heaven & Earth's Code
I wonder who are we going to send
for the martial art's competition?
Have you decided yet?
White Dragon
the Master is soundly asleep
Let's not disturb him
Let's go
Haven't arrive yet?
Waiting for who?
Ning, be careful!
Are you alright?
Go, go, go, go!
How can anyone be so careless?
Just sped out suddenly.
How is it?
The bike is broken.
We'll just have to walk up the moutain road.
Ok.
Daddy, was that a taoist priest?
I think he is.
I felt that he is very compassionate.
Let's go.
Sui He-Yi, you're late.
Brother,
I...
Why is the water so little?
Brother ,
half way on the road,
I encountered a car,
and was nearly knock down by it
That is why the water ...
You don't have to lie to me.
You know the rules laid down
by White Dragon priest is very strict
Go over there and pluck out all the weeds
Yes, brother.
How are you....
We are here to participate in
the martial art's competition
Taoist Xie is gone!
Go, go, go. Quick!
What is it?
The head priest is gone.
Uncle, the head priest is gone.
Excuse me...
The head priest have no more pulse.
The head priest have passed on.
We are all very sad.
Life is just but a glimpse.
I believe,
he have attained nivarna and
have ascended
Who is he?
He is the martial art
competition sponsor
Mr. Tang Yun Long
Even though the head priest's vital
signs are gone
But if I am not wrong,
he is using Turtle Relaxation technique.
According to western science
Is temporary hibernation.
Hibernation?
Yes.
He's gone into a state of nothingness,
just like a deity.
The head priest's powers is
beyond prediction
Taoist Xie
Taoist Xie has awaken!
Head Priest, you have awakened.
Thank God!
OK! OK!
You've arrived.
You've finally arrived.
Everyone,
Sui He-Yi is Wu Dang's representative.
You're really great
The head priest came alive again.
You again!
Sui He-Yi is only a lay disciple,
Even he know a bit of martial art
but it is not sufficient
Besides, there are others more senior
It wouldn't be his turn to represent.
Yes.
Yes,he is right,
Head Priest Xie.
My kung fu is inadequate,
and not up to par.
My only desire is to take
of my mother
and to cure her sickness
Such a important task.
I won't be able to undertake it
To be able to do and not doing,
To be able to walk and not walking.
Head priest,
If he were to represent,
we are bound to lose
Besides,
once, every 500 years competition
Wu Dang cannot lose face
To lose is to win,
To win is to lose.
Make good the preparation
Fight!
No way!
I haven't ask my mother yet!
What you're hold is the treasure map,right?
No, there isn't any treasure map?
Unless,
you came here to rob treasures?
I'm very sorry, priest
I've lost my way
May I ask, if this is Blissful Palace?
I am not a priest.
My dear Auntie, the priest you are
looking for is over there
Hello priest, how are you?
It's like this
I am a representative of Pin Jin
of 2 town, 2 provinces
I am here for the competition.
My junior is sick.
So, I took his place.
My name is Tien Xin
and not auntie at all.
To commemorate the renovation of Wu Dang
500 years anniversary
and the reconstruction of the Five Dragon Place
Today, a competition is held for
young martial artists
Representatives from the whole of China
Oversea's Chinese organisation's representatives
With the spirit to promote Taoism
To encourage youth to learn
leadership, learning and dissemination,
To attend this conference.
Representative from Sichuan,
Kong Tong sect - Wei Chuen Yang
His opponent, from Bei Ping,
Tianjin, Dragon's Gate sect, Tien Xin
I never fight with women
Qucikly, go home.
The biggest mistake in your life,
is to despised women.
This is called Cannon Hammer.
If you got struck by that blow,
that will be disastrous.
If you meet an opponent like this,
Don't fight and just admit defeat.
You think that this sister
will lose for sure?
Good! Good! Good!
Good! Fantatic! Good!
What sister is using,
is it Southern Tai Chi?
What technique is this?
Could it be...
the rumored secret technique from
Master Zhang San Feng - Silkworm Form?
The form is but the essence isn't.
Silkworm Form?
Good! Great! Good!
Tien Xin won.
Good! Good! Good!
Second match
From America's National Taoist
Association, Tang Ning
Daughter, Dad brought you here is just
to broaden your view
Don't be too serious.
If you can't win, just admit defeat.
Daddy, my ears are numb.
Then don't use your ears
Just watch my hands.
Good! Good! Good!
Tang Ning won
Pain?
Bear it for a while.
Daddy will be more gentle
Just bear it for a while.
Daddy, did I win beautifully?
You still dare to say
You promised me just to play a while,
then admit defeat
You fought too seriously.
My heart keeps pounding while watching.
But
Dad, whatever you do,
you are very serious
Why did you tell me not
to be serious?
It's okay now.
It's getting late.
It's time for Daddy to go to the
male dormitory to rest
Have an early night.
Daddy?
What kind of sickness did Mummy
contracted and left us?
Actually,
I like to know how you and mummy
know each other
Didn't I told you before.
I used to have a pigtail
during the Ching Dynasty
After that,
I crossed the sea to America,
met your mother in a Chinese restaurant
It's enough
It's late.
Rest early.
Daddy, when you came to Wu Dang
with the treasure map
I felt that you are troubled
Did you really brought me here just
to appraise martial arts?
I...
brought you here for match-making.
Daddy, you're disgusting.
Daughter, don't be angry.
Golden Hall
Southern Rocks
Dragon Sword with Seven Powers
like a treasure mountain
Five Dragon Palace?
Dad.
Your daddy died young
If not, you would be married with kids
My health is also not good.
Mum, don't forget
We are at Wudang Mountain,
This is a magical mountain.
With healing powers
Your sickness can certainly be cured.
Now, my only wish is
to find you a wife.
Daddy, you promised me
that we will be partners once
we are in Wudang mountain
right?
I am not your Dad.
- What is it?
- Nothing, mum!
Do not be afraid.
Mum, don't be afraid
Who are you?
You again
What! You know her?
She is a guest of Taoist priest Xie.
It's a young woman
Son, you don't have to get ordained.
Lady,
are you alright?
Young lady!
Tien Xin,
Tsuen Tien sword is our tribe's
sacred relic
It was forged from asteroid rocks
It has very strong powers.
Your father went to China
to search for the sword
but after many years,
there is no news of him
When we found his body in the desert
his hand is still holding this pearl
It must be connected to the
where abouts of the sacred sword
When you grow up,
you must complete your Dad's duty
Thief!
There is an accomplice.
Go quickly.
Young lady, you've awakened.
I am very worried
You fell from the roof.
I was afraid that you might be
paralyzed like me
I'm so sorry
that I damaged your roof.
My dad will pay you
No need to pay.
I've repaired it.
Aren't you the Wudang representative?
I am also a representative
I won today.
We might be competiting against
each other.
I won't go and compete.
Why?
I have to take care of my mother.
Aiya,
hurry up and get married
then you won't have to take care of me.
Young lady
What is your name?
Tang Ning.
Ning Er,
this is my son.
he's called Sui He-Yi,
and still not married.
How about you?
Mum, the lady is still young.
Don't scare her.
Not that young..
Mum, have an early night.
Son,
both of you are very compatible.
I'm sleeping immediately.
Have a nice chat
I won't hear a thing.
Ok, ok, sleep tight.
Lady,
I think you've lost your way
Don't always call me lady
My name is Tang Ning.
Mosquitoes are pests.
Pest also have a life.
Besides, I've made a wish
that if my mum's illness is cured
I won't kill any living thing.
When the night comes,
and the weather is cool
there won't be any mosquitoes
Actually, humans
is part of the universe.
Mosquitoes too
All things in the world too.
Lay disciple needs to learn the "way"?
In fact, I'm very stupid.
Taoist priest Xie,
taught me the "Way",
and that all things are one
He taught me meditation
and said we can feel "life"
I am really no good at it.
Can you feel it?
I just felt that,
I've got no life now.
It's you
Aren't you the sponsor?
and I have to rescue you
If not for me,
you will surely be caught.
Stop boasting
I am the one who saved you.
If not for my last attack,
can you escape?
You came here to steal?
The sacred sword belongs to our tribe
I've been searching for it for years.
Then things is easier.
In total, Wudang have 7 treasures
I have a suggestion.
Let's co-operate.
Once the job is done. The sword belongs to you.
All the rest will belong to me
You have tested White Dragon's
prowess earlier on.
With your strenght alone,
you won't be able to succeed
Let's do it together.
Do you dare?
Why not?
But our personality is different.
I came here to get back what
belongs to me.
You are here to steal.
But when you steal,
why did you bring your daughter here?
What you are doing might cause harm to her.
What did you say?
Killed my daughter?
When I just came out,
She thought I was you,
chasing behind me.
Finally, fell off the cliff.
But don't worry,
I think she is now ...
This is Wudang Mountain,
it has healing energy.
It can cure any disease.
Ning Er!
Ning Er! Ning Er!
Daddy, what happen to you?
Are you alright?
Didn't you fell from the cliff?
Yes I did.
Fortunately,
I used my internal energy to protect me
Look at me, I'm alright.
You frightened me to death.
Yunnan, Da Mao sect - Liu Kun won.
The next match,
Seoul, Chuen Zhen's representative - Li Tsuen De.
His opponent from Shangdong,
Peng Lai sect - Zhang Yang
Li Tsuen De won.
The last match for today,
America's Taoist Association's
representative - Tang Ning
Ning Er, remember what I said.
If you can't win, just admit defeat.
Okay, okay.
I won't give way.
You also do your best.
Don't let your father down.
Come on!
I've lost
Thanks for giving way
Tang Ning won
You are lucky you didn't lose,
Where are you going?
It's a secret.
Professor Tang
Last night, why did you go up the mountain?
I've got no face to back to
Chiang Dong to see the elders
I'm sorry.
Did I hit you?
Miss Tien Xin
Did you have a good sleep last night?
No good.
I had a nightmare.
Mum, bear with it.
Sui He-Yi!
Mum, we're reaching.
Bear with it.
If I guess correctly,
the two of us are under
White Dragon's suspicion
That is why in the competition
you deliberately lost the match.
By using daylight for our operation
White Dragon is unable to leave now
No time to keep vigil on the sword
We have bigger plans.
We will have to follow the next verse
to get to our next target
Truth Sutra and Heavenly Pill
Hey,
Why don't you continue to
get the sacred sword?
I'm not that stupid
Once you've got the sword,
you would leave.
Truth Sutra,
should be the 5,000 verse of the
Dao De Sutra by Lao Tzu
Hidden in Blissful Palace.
Another treasure is the Heavenly Pill.
Made by Taoist Zhang
said to cure all illness.
Hidden in ...
Prince hides in the dragon bed
What's so great about it?
Hide the heavenly pill.
Poetry is actually so simple.
Why don't we split up.
OK.
If you think you can act alone...
I have no objection .
You go get the Sutra,
I will go and get the Heavenly Pill.
Why do I have to get the Sutra?
Because I've checked
There are only 2 priest guarding
the Blissful Palace
It's relatively easier to operate.
The biggest mistake of your life
is to despise.....
I'm just joking with you.
Wu Dang is full of skilled pugilist
You've better be careful.
Before the sun sets,
we'll see who complete first.
Mum, you're awake.
Mum has woken.
Miss Tang Ning. Miss Tang Ning
Auntie.
All the meridians and channels
in her body are cleared
Only the heart is not cleared
Good, you are cured
You can get out of bed
and walk around.
I can get out of bed and walk?
Try it.
Mum,
Try it, give it a go.
One, two, three.
Very good.
Mum, you really can walk again.
Aiya, I can move.
Sit down first.
I can really walk.
Thank heaven.When the bad is gone,
fortune will come.
Your mother's illness is alright now.
Thank you, head priest.
Thank you.
Now you can compete for Wudang
without worries
I ...
You don't have to be ordained.
Go and compete without worries.
Go and thank the head priest
and show your gratitude
I know.
Who is it?
Pursue him.
Stand still
Please forgive me
Thank you very much.
How are you, head priest.
I am a disciple of Si-Yue, Hua Mountain,
Ninth Heavenly Palace.
Is it convenient for us to talk?
Head priest, to tell the truth
The nunnery....
I think the one we had was Ying Sutra
and yours is the Yang Sutra.
I thought since the
Ying Sutra was stolen...
your Yang Sutra might be stolen too...
Haha, you've been fooled.
You've been fooled.
That's it!
Strange.
Not even one taoist priest
Remember, the preparations for my
my plan will not be in vain
The sutra is really hidden here?
I hope it's not a trap
"Dao De Sutra"
What kind of treasure is this?
So easy to get hold of.
My acting and my kung fu
have no usage at all.
Wasted my time practicing
Great bandit,Tang Yun Long
You're late.
You've lost.
Nun Tien Xin, you've won.
You are injured.
You are also injured.
The priest you talk about is really skillful
I nearly can't escape.
Here!
It's already rusty.
Don't know why it's called a treasure.
Eh, look here.
Let's proceed to our next target.
Outside the cave of the Eight
Meridian hides the black leader.
Didn't you say that poetry is simple?
Explain.
It is that simple.
Yes...
The eight pulse....
I think that there are 2 treasures.
You see, the Eight Meridian,
Perhaps it's the Eight Meridian in a cave
Black leader...
Maybe the head is pitch black...
Black Leader..... Shou Wu [Polygonim multiflorum]
Wu Dang Mountain is known for it
fertile land and healing energy
A pair of thousand year old Ho Shou Wu
is growing here
Just a pair?
There are many thousand year old Ho Shou Wu.
and they are husband and wife,
quarreled frequently.
That's why I dislike men,
I still like to be alone.
Women are more troublesome.
I like to be independent.
Right. We will always be on different paths.
After we've stolen the treasures
You can sell them and make money
and I can go home.
I am not the greedy
selfish type, who would die for money
Okay, don't waste my time.
Don't think that you are so self righteous
If you think that the sacred sword
belongs to your tribe,
bring out some proof.
The sacred was originally from our tribe.
Proof?
Even if there is no proof.
The sword still belongs to our tribe.
Okay.
Without you, I can still find
the sacred sword.
I can!
Sleeping Kung Fu, is the higher skill for
internal sect of martial arts.
Zhuang Tzu dreamt and became a butterfly
The butterfly dreamt and became Zhuang Tzu.
Grandmaster Chen Chuan slept for 800 years
for the youth of Sung Dynasty
Beggar Su Qi Er slept,
and learned Drunken LuoHan Fist.
Close your eyes,
Open your eyes,
A day will pass.
Sleep deity. Sleep deity.
When the rock takes hold,
all the years will be forgotten.
The 3 Rays goes deeper,
your nature will be pure.
Breathing and relaxation becomes natural
This is Grandmaster Zhang San Feng's
Sleeping Kung Fu's technique
You must always remember it.
Something happened in Crouching Dragon's hall
Head priest have not waken
from his practice
What is it?
The 7 of us pursued him
but he escaped.
Any urgent things that you are seeing
the head priest?
A robber appeared in
Crouching Dragon's hall.
What have been stolen?
Nothing is stolen.
The thief is using an incense bag,
Took away a ball like object.
Auntie,
Why did you suddently let Sui He-Yi compete?
We are indebted to Head Priest Xie,
Of course we have to return the favor.
Last night, I dreamt that I and
Sui He-Yi was on a Baqua stage,
just like a marriage ceremony.
Bowing?
No, no, nothing at all.
Ning Er,
open the box near my bed and have a look.
It's beautiful.
I've never worn such Chinese clothes before.
Quick wear it and have a look.
How is it?
You've made the right choice.
It is fated.
This is what my mother made for my marriage.
Beautiful. Aiyaa, beautiful.
It seems that I am disturbing your sleep.
Why are you wearing my mother's clothes?
She gave it to me.
Beautiful?
It's beautiful.
Where's my mother?
She is asleep.
I came here to find you.
I am practicing kung fu here.
Thank you for taking care of my mother.
I'm happy to do it.
Actually, old folks are like children
She listens to my stories.
After a while she fell asleep.
You and your mother depended on each other
Me and my father too.
These few years, only he taught me martial arts
and how to take care of my body
He've done some research,
the most scientific way to take care of
the body is the Taoist way
I talk too much.
Don't worry about your mother
I will visit her when I am free.
Stretch out your hand.
Close your eyes.
This treasure of mine,
have helped Head Priest Xie.
Give to you.
What is it?
Just a little worm.
What's the big deal?
Yunnan, Da Mou sect - Liu Kun,
against,
America's Chinese Taoist Association's
Tang Ning.
Daughter...
Daddy, with you around,
I am confident.
Tang Yun Long, come with me.
Why? I can't go.
Look over there.
They're looking for you.
Don't worry. If I can't win,
I'll just admit defeat
You guys go.
Hurry up.
Boss, Tang Yun Long is over there.
Follow him.
If necessary, kill him.
Yes.
I am fine, don't worry.
Most responsible father, wake up!
We've been followed.
They are not from Wudang.
Their shoes are not the same
Don't care about them.
Let's go quickly!
Tang Ning won.
I think this is Eight Meridian cave.
There's a lot of people welcoming us.
You sneak in from the Dragon's Head.
We will lure the two groups of people
to the forest on the left.
Stand still! Stand still!
Don't run! Stand still!
Let's go!
It's clearly stated that it's
Eight Meridian Palace.
Why did it says Eight Meridian Cave?
Don't think we are wrong.
This treasure is connected to
the eight meridian
It's only broken idols.
Which is the treasure?
It must be here.
Let's search quickly.
You think you can distract them
and lure them away?
I've waited for you for a long time.
Professor Tang.
All yours.
Me?
If I fight with women,
I will definitely be at a disadvantage.
I ... I ...
I will not tear my own clothes
and pretend that I'm injured.
Go find your treasure in your rubbish.
Please hurry up, for goodness sake!
Eight Meridian...
is it 8 strings of golden wheat?
Or is it 20% discount?
Eight Meridian
It's 7 Channel & 8 Meridian.
Have you found it yet?
Look at my strike.
I've found it.
Tien Xin
I found the golden man.
Tang Yun Long
You didn't expect that I didn't die
I am very sorry
that I messed up your leg.
Know that you owe me a lot.
hand over the golden man
and your backpack.
Attack!
Take the golden man and go
I will take care of them
If we go, we'll go together.
If we fight, we fight together.
Be careful.
Your sleep kung fu is so lousy?
You will definitely lose, if you fight.
It's not that sleep kung fu is so lousy,
my intellect is too low
The reason why I am here
is to find a cure for my mother.
The worm that you wanted to give me the last time,
do you still want to give it to me?
You're not afraid any more?
Not any more.
Here!
I'm not afraid...
Is because I know when it grows,
it'll become a butterfly
Now, it can only crawl on the ground
But if it turns into a butterfly,
It can fly in the air.
It's like stepping into another dimension.
Man sleeps and dreams
is also like going into another dimension?
Dreams?
Butterflies?
Another dimension?
It's like this,
Imagine your mother's illness is cured
and you feel very good.
You are like the leaves.
Floating in the wind,
just like butterflies
going where it wants to go.
Aaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhh.......
Thank you.
I felt my heart cleared a lot.
Heaven and man are one!
Such a beautiful leaf.
Let me have a look.
I'm not letting you see.
Brother Sui,
if one is to die,
won't it be like sleeping?
What I mean is,
maybe one day,
I'm to leave this world
will we meet in another place?
Young lady, what nonsense are you talking?
I've got a strange sickness
It's genetic
Can't be cured.
My mother and grandmother
died because of this sickness
They died very young.
I'm not afraid of death.
I just hate myself for being useless.
No...
You won't die.
You really won't die.
Okay, no more unhappy talk.
Now, when I am healthy
I have a great desire.
Tomorrow's final match,
want to have a good match with you.
Just like me and my classmates,
attending a graduation ceremony.
OK?
OK.
Man of your words
You have to keep your word.
Liars are dogs!
Do you know that
there are 3 treasure mountains?
The fourth verse is 'thunder and fire'
should be Thunder and Fire hall.
In the dancing clouds,
must be 'Music and Dance'
If "Between the Dancing Clouds" means
the golden top of Cloud Sea
Take a look.
The North Star & Seven Constellation
Outside the cave of the Eight
Meridian hides the black leader.
This place is outside the Eight Meridian Cave
and where Ho Shou Wu grows the most lush.
Isn't Ho Shou Wu the treasure?
How can the treasure
be found all over the mountain?
Are you Ho Shou Wu?
Are you?
Actually, what we are finding is
the ground of Wudang's spirit.
Legend has it that it sticks to
the roots of Ho Shou Wu
just like the veins of the human body.
Likewise, connecting to every mountain in Wudang.
What's more magical,
they can sense the human heart
change into human shape.
But,
do you feel that,
we got hold of these treasures too easily?
furthermore, our treasure maps are identical
That is why...
you suspect that the map...
Maybe, I'm too suspicious
I've lost confidence in man
and lots of things
At least you believe that the
heavenly pill can resurrect the dead
I'm researching science,
don't believe what that cannot be
scientifically proven.
But later I discover
that many things can't be explained with science
and many sickness that cannot be
treated with science
I really want to find the spirit
of the Ho Shou Wu
but there are no leads.
Didn't you just said that Ho Shou Wu
can sense the the heart of man?
You can try use your heart to find it.
This is after all a myth.
But you said earlier,
There are many things that science
cannot explain.
North Start and the 7 Constellation
I remembered what my grandfather told me
Every time a family member leaves
They will turn into a star
To protect their closest kin.
So when I have a wish,
I will make a wish upon the star.
Please try it.
It really appears.
Honest heart makes the spirit appears.
It's written in the Trees and Grass log,
that red is the female and
white is the male
Can't imagine that a husband and wife
pair appears.
Caught them!
Smells good.
Ning Er, you've arrived.
Where is Brother Sui?
He went to pick firewood.
Heavenly Emperor, please bless
bless Ning Er's sickness
will soon be cured.
I am willing to have her
sickness instead of her.
I beg you.
Hungry?
Let's go.
I came to find my father,
Professor Tang Yun Long.
Can you ask him to come out for a while?
We are also looking for him.
Please go back to your bedroom.
Don't come out.
Your father won't come back tonight.
He is alright.
He is just afraid
that you might be worried
That's why he asked me to come
and see you.
I know.
I'll take good care of myself.
Sister Tien Xin,
I'm really lucky.
Tommorrow, I will be in the finals.
Daddy...
can he come and watch?
Ning Er,
Your daddy is stealing the treasures
because of you
Do you know that?
I know.
Now,
A lot of priests are looking for him.
My father is a great person.
But this time
He steals from others,
all because of me
Sleep early,
you have a match tomorrow.
I'm scared...
Do you believe in miracles?
Before,
I always thought,
if you only have faith,
and with hope in the heart,
Then I will have a good life.
Now I discovered,
you can't change reality
with faith and hope.
Sister Tien Xin,
look at my dad ...
He don't believe in miracles before
but now he does because of me.
You...
are a little girl living a hard life
Just like your dad.
He's actually hiding...
but in front of you
he had to act nonchalant and smile.
Sister Tien Xin,
can you do me a favor?
Help me realize my last wish.
Don't say sad things.
You just have to keep on living
and I'll help you with anything.
You have to keep your word.
Get married to my dad.
After my mother died
my dad...
seldom smile.
But I can tell,
when you are with him
He is very happy.
This......
I hate to be tied down.
I can't help you with this.
I'm frightened....
maybe one day,
only my daddy is left in this world
I really ...
I really don't want to
abandon him
You are crying again?
Poor child...
Your dad won't be left alone, ok?
"Golden Hall"
Great master,
indeed,
they hide in high places,
where they can be found.
We'll talk after we go down the mountain.
Go down the mountain?
I just climbed up!
Tang Yun Long and
the girl have disappeared.
Do you think they've taken
the treasures and ran off?
His daughter is here.
He can't run away
I say we kill Tang Yun Long,
take one or two treasure
and that will be enough.
No way.
The 7 treasures have to be
gathered together at the same time
it's value
weighs more that power and riches.
The treasure map that we created,
and distributed to the world.
Not only attracts Tang Yun Long,
and the thing that have been
missing for many years,
Stilling Wind Pearl.
Brother Sui,
Today we can finally stand here together.
Ning Er,
Can we not fight?
I'll admit defeat.
You promised me.
Man of your words
You have to keep your word.
Liars are dogs
Don't, don't ...
Don't fight anymore.
Ning Er.
In the ring....
if I can stand for one more minute
I'll live for one minute more.
Fight
Let's fight.
OK.
It is clearly a stone sword.
Why call it a sacred sword?
a very mysterious magnetic mineral.
There is nothing like that on earth.
Pardon me.
Look!
This is the symbol of our tribe.
Now we go to Golden Peak Hall
to take the Thunder Needle
the only thing left is the
Stilling Wind Pearl.
Don't go just yet.
I heard that the Thunder Needle
will invoke thunder
Very dangerous.
Thunder Needle is to attract electricity
from the thunder and disperse it into the ground
That is why, gold from the Golden Hall
for 500 years have been having
thunder and lightning,
It still remains intact.
You've got the sacred sword
You intent to go home now?
I'll definitely take the sacred sword home.
But not now...
I promised Ning Er
I'll wait for her sickness to
be cured first
She already knows...
Hmm.
I thought I can hide it from her
and let her live happily while
she is still alive.
That's why, even though her sickness
have worsen,
she still kept it from you.
and let you be happier.
Ning Er is an understanding child.
Bring the golden needle here.
Ning Er.
Taoist Xie.
This is not internal injury
It's a strange sickness.
Pulses are in disarray.
Internal organs are bleeding.
Taoist Xie,
Even my mother's sickness can be cured.
You certainly have a way to
cure Ning Er.
In luck there is a high and a low,
There is also long and short life.
Ning Er
Ning Er!
Ning Er.
Dad is here.
Dad.
Ning Er.
This time I did listen to you
I've lost the match.
From now on...
Don't you have the heavenly pill
that can resurrect the dead?
What are you thinking about?
But the 7 treasures are incomplete
Don't know if it's effective?
Don't think so much!
Just try it!
Quick!
Tang Yun Long!
You really came back for your daughter.
It's time to settle our debt.
Let me save my daughter first...
All the treasures are mine!
Throw the treasures over here.
Or else I'll kill your daughter first.
Hurry up!
Still missing this?
Am I right?
White Dragon
Thunder Needle is a sacred relic
of Golden Peak.
You're crazy!
I'm not crazy.
Everything goes according to my plan.
This is destiny.
This is what 'Heaven and Man are One'
really means.
You want to become the head priest
you won't have long to wait.
Do you really think I want
to be the head priest?
Aiya, you really underestimated me.
The only thing missing from
Wudang 7 Treasures...
I've planned for so many years
just so that someone would send the
Stilling Wind Pearl back to me.
That's the necklace that grandfather
gave it to me.
It's really the Stilling Wind Pearl?
Back then, your father, Tien-Yu and I
came to Wu Dang,
To retrieve the sacred relic,
Tsuen Tien Sacred Sword
Half way he discovered the secret
that I want to collect the 7 treasures
is to achieve Nirvana.
That's why he stole the Stilling Wind Pearl
To spoil my plan.
But,
he did not realize,
that I've actually collected 6 Treasures.
Finally,
I just used a shoddy map
to let her daughter
to bring back the Stilling Wind Pearl.
To reach nirvana takes practice.
White Dragon
what you're doing is demonic.
Ning Er is dying.
Ning Er.
I'm frightened...
Don't be afraid.
7 Treasures put together,
I can finally attain Nirvana.
7 Treasures are leaving the mountain
Yin and Yang have lost it's balance.
I dreamt of Wudang's disaster
It has really came.
No one can stop me anymore.
Heavenly Pill in orbit,
will be completed in time.
Very soon,
I will attain nirvana.
Taoist Xie,
Ning Er can't hang on much longer.
We have to quickly snatch back
the Heavenly Pill.
The highest stage of Sleep Kung Fu is
"Body without Attachment"
Spirit becomes nothingness.
just like the state White Dragon
is in now.
[In an Altered State of pure Emptiness]
White Dragon,
no one ever dare to fool me before!
We'll have to get the Heavenly Pill back
Do you want to take a risk
and try?
Sleep Deity, Sleep Deity.
When the rock takes hold,
all the years will be forgotten..
The 3 Rays goes deeper,
your nature will be pure.
Breathing and relaxation becomes natural.
Taoist priest!
Quick, use the Heavenly Pill
to save Ning Er.
Mere mortals!
How can you compete with me!
Daughter
Daddy! Daddy...
Daddy...
Ning Er
It's alright now.
Tien Xin.
Tang Yun Lon
You are a tough man,
but once mention about your daughter,
you became soft.
Sister Tien Xin,
Sacred Sword
Let it remain in Wudang Mountain.
I have no need to go home now.
Because the sacred sword
has its own home now.
My heart,
also have a home now.
Thank you...
guys.
Sister Tien Xin
Sister Tien Xin.
Thursday she held in the hand \ NLA treasure map game.
What treasure map?
She came to steal the sacred sword?
The sacred sword originally belongs to our tribe.
The biggest mistake in your life
is to despise...
I am just joking.
Wudang have many skilled pugilists.
You've better be careful.
I remembered grandfather once told me,
Whenever a kin leaves,
They will turn into stars
To protect their closest kin.
Sister Tien Xin.